<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</title>
    <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 16:21:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning is more than passing Exams!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/learning-is-more-than-studying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 16:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/learning-is-more-than-studying/</guid>
      <description>Learning is what keeps us alive. Learning is one of the many things that gives unique identity among each other, with the skills, we learned so far in our life, our behavior, mindset and logical reasoning skills, they are all learned by us, throughout our life, consciously or otherwise. It might be one of the things that makes us who we are, make us human, make us alive. In my opinion, if someone is not learning (anything) in their life, they are not living it and guess what, leanring doesn&#39;t always mean to study text books and pass examinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Coffee!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/connecting-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 01:01:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/connecting-coffee/</guid>
      <description>All coders/programmers are night owlers and prefer coffee to sustain the whole night. And here is something interesting for everyone who sustains on coffee. There is a special protocol made for all programmers whose primary Energy drink is coffee, named Hyper Text Coffee Pot Control Protocol. Let&#39;s start with, what is this coffee protocol?
Rationale The rationale for making a standard protocol for all coffee driven programmers is too connect all these coffee pots along with their hosts (programmers) with each other using Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naruto vs DBZ!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/naruto-vs-dbz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 22:22:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/naruto-vs-dbz/</guid>
      <description>Naruto vs Dragon Ball Z! Yes, You guessed it right. It&#39;s the comparison between naruto vs Dragon Ball Z in the world of anime. It is true that even though most of you have already watched Naruto, Naruto Shippuden and Boruto, I haven&#39;t even finished my Naruto series. But now I regret, why I didn&#39;t watch this amazing series that pumps my blood even in the most sensual, non-action scenes. I didn&#39;t watch Naruto before because of its reputation of very lengthy series and I didn&#39;t want to Torrent Download or Torrent Stream these many episodes (I try to avoid torrenting as much as possible).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible101</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/ansible101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 19:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/ansible101/</guid>
      <description>In the realm of Devops, where there is always fight to provide the better and efficient ways of production in an enterprise, Ansible is one of the solution to help enterprise achieve that. This blog post will brief you about what ansible is and how learning ansible can save hours of debugging and setting up the same configurations again and again. Later this post will brief the &amp;ldquo;Ansible 101&amp;rdquo; session taken by @trishna_g at #dgplug on freenode server, IRC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog announcement</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/blog-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 14:33:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/blog-announcement/</guid>
      <description>My voice! We all have something to say and share our views with others, right? We all want to speak our opinions without any hesitation, and share our point of view, don&#39;t we? And still, at times we don&#39;t share everything we want to. We all have something to say, don&#39;t we? And we all speak our feelings, our emotions whenever we want to share something with someone, right?
But at times, based on the situation, either we don&#39;t put forward our feelings, our views and stays silent, which is by the way, not good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old is Gold!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/older-posts.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 13:07:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/older-posts.md/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for posts older than the ones present here? You can find them at https://phi2infinity.blogspot.in. All the older posts will be updated there only. I may or may not migrate the posts back to this website. Meanwhile all my writings are compiled at one place on github.
To know more, read the moving announcement here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>