<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>others on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</title>
    <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/categories/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in others on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 22:22:56 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theknowledgeseeker.in/categories/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Naruto vs DBZ!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/naruto-vs-dbz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 22:22:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/naruto-vs-dbz/</guid>
      <description>Naruto vs Dragon Ball Z! Yes, You guessed it right. It&#39;s the comparison between naruto vs Dragon Ball Z in the world of anime. It is true that even though most of you have already watched Naruto, Naruto Shippuden and Boruto, I haven&#39;t even finished my Naruto series. But now I regret, why I didn&#39;t watch this amazing series that pumps my blood even in the most sensual, non-action scenes. I didn&#39;t watch Naruto before because of its reputation of very lengthy series and I didn&#39;t want to Torrent Download or Torrent Stream these many episodes (I try to avoid torrenting as much as possible).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Age is just a number!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/age-is-just-a-number/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 20:54:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/age-is-just-a-number/</guid>
      <description>Experience is what matters, we all grow, little by little each day, but not because we grow older physically. It&#39;s not the age, that make us older, it is the experience we all have every day.
This blog post is about Experiences.
Naruto, he grew a little more.
SUSE package hub project, even though, I didn&#39;t have much of the practical experience on the project of packaging, but still I had a lot more to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog announcement</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/blog-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 14:33:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/blog-announcement/</guid>
      <description>My voice! We all have something to say and share our views with others, right? We all want to speak our opinions without any hesitation, and share our point of view, don&#39;t we? And still, at times we don&#39;t share everything we want to. We all have something to say, don&#39;t we? And we all speak our feelings, our emotions whenever we want to share something with someone, right?
But at times, based on the situation, either we don&#39;t put forward our feelings, our views and stays silent, which is by the way, not good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old is Gold!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/older-posts.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 13:07:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/older-posts.md/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for posts older than the ones present here? You can find them at https://phi2infinity.blogspot.in. All the older posts will be updated there only. I may or may not migrate the posts back to this website. Meanwhile all my writings are compiled at one place on github.
To know more, read the moving announcement here.
I am listing down all the posts available there with their title and the hyperlink to the original blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>