<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>insights on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</title>
    <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/categories/insights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in insights on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 15:03:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theknowledgeseeker.in/categories/insights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The scope of improvement!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/short-posts/scope-of-improvement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 15:03:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/short-posts/scope-of-improvement/</guid>
      <description>When someone says, they have mastered some skill/concept/subject and agrees, that they are perfect in that particular domain. They are wrong!
There is always some scope for improvement. We can always improve our skills, knowledge, personality, projects and everything. But how do one know where is one lacking and needs improvement? How can one tell if they have really mastered something?
That is simple. Answer the most simple questions we avoid on daily basis and you will know if you really understand the thing you think you know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning is more than passing Exams!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/learning-is-more-than-studying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 16:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/learning-is-more-than-studying/</guid>
      <description>Learning is copying!
We learn by copying others&amp;rsquo; work, patterns and make new patterns using the knowledge gained by mimicing others.
Learning is what keeps us alive. Learning is one of the many things that gives the unique identity we have with the skills, we learned so far in our life, our behavior, mindset and logical reasoning skills gained throughout our life, consciously or otherwise. It might be one of the things that makes us who we are, make us human, make us alive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
