<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</title>
    <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:42:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Work Work Work!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/hire-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 16:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/hire-me/</guid>
      <description>I am always up for working on new challenges. If you feel I can help you out with your problem, feel free to reach out to me with the details.
I am skilled in Linux development and Python software development practices with knowledge of cloud services. I have experience deploying different projects with CI/CD pipelines on AWS. I can provide consultancy services for your project architecture, infrastructure and help with task management within the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read more!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/more-about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 13:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/more-about-me/</guid>
      <description>Nice to see you here and thank you for showing interest to know me. One word to describe me would be &amp;ldquo;philomath&amp;rdquo;.
Yes, a philomath. A single word that describes me and my thirst for knowledge. Philomath originates from combining 2 greek words, &amp;ldquo;Philos and &amp;ldquo;math&amp;rdquo; that means, &amp;ldquo;lover of learning&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;knowledge seeker&amp;rdquo;.
I love to learn new tools, techniques, concepts and everything that is fascinating. I learn from everyone and everything and don&amp;rsquo;t mind a constructive criticism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Now?</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/what-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 12:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/what-now/</guid>
      <description>#OpenToWork I am working as a backend software engineer at Essentia Softserv LLP since July, 2021. I am working on django based web application to perform batch processing. Other than this, I am mostly reading the books listed below. I visited United States in month of May to attend Pycon US 2022. It was a nice experience. I may or may not write blog post about my experience.
I enrolled in a computer architecture MOOC on coursera by Princeton University.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
