<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philomath&#39;s Lair!</title>
    <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Philomath&#39;s Lair!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 16:21:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://theknowledgeseeker.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning is more than passing Exams!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/learning-is-more-than-studying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 16:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/learning-is-more-than-studying/</guid>
      <description>Learning is what keeps us alive. Learning is one of the many things that gives unique identity among each other, with the skills, we learned so far in our life, our behavior, mindset and logical reasoning skills, they are all learned by us, throughout our life, consciously or otherwise. It might be one of the things that makes us who we are, make us human, make us alive. In my opinion, if someone is not learning (anything) in their life, they are not living it and guess what, leanring doesn&amp;rsquo;t always mean to study text books and pass examinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 01:01:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact me! Contact me at the following links or fill this form to get in touch.
I am digitally omnipresent and can be contacted anywhere, as long as the context matters. Following are my profiles that can be used to contact:
 Twitter: @miphilomath Gitub: @miphilomath Instagram: @miphilomath IRC: philomath on #dgplug, #learnandteach on freenode server Keybase: @philomath Mail me at philomath [ @ ] [disroot] [dot] [org]  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pick your dare!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/pick-your-dare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 22:56:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/pick-your-dare/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s just an idea.
Ever stuck confused thinking on what project to pick up next when you have lots of ideas and only a weekend to work on? Well it is common problem with me.
Image of my pick your dare!
What can be your dare?
 Projects Blogs to write Books to read Hobbies to pick  Software version? Well, we can have everything in software, even the reality (matrix) but I love the game of picking the dare with something physical like lottery or waffle ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Coffee!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/connecting-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 01:01:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/connecting-coffee/</guid>
      <description>All coders/programmers are night owlers and prefer coffee to sustain the whole night. And here is something interesting for everyone who sustains on coffee. There is a special protocol made for all programmers whose primary Energy drink is coffee, named Hyper Text Coffee Pot Control Protocol. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with, what is this coffee protocol?
Rationale The rationale for making a standard protocol for all coffee driven programmers is too connect all these coffee pots along with their hosts (programmers) with each other using Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naruto vs DBZ!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/others/naruto-vs-dbz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 22:22:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/others/naruto-vs-dbz/</guid>
      <description>Naruto vs Dragon Ball Z! Yes, You guessed it right. It&amp;rsquo;s the comparison between naruto vs Dragon Ball Z in the world of anime. It is true that even though most of you have already watched Naruto, Naruto Shippuden and Boruto, I haven&amp;rsquo;t even finished my Naruto series. But now I regret, why I didn&amp;rsquo;t watch this amazing series that pumps my blood even in the most sensual, non-action scenes. I didn&amp;rsquo;t watch Naruto before because of its reputation of very lengthy series and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to Torrent Download or Torrent Stream these many episodes (I try to avoid torrenting as much as possible).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The month of OSS &amp; to get lost!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/the-month-of-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:33:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/the-month-of-oss/</guid>
      <description>October is the month of open source for me. Want to know why? In this blog post, I am going to share my Open Source Experience in the month of October 2018, when attended, Open Source Summit Europe 2018, Scotlug meetup and MozFest Festival as well :)
This blog post is a long due, waiting in my draft for ages, for me to complete it and hit publish. Last year, in the month of October, I got to experience the most out of the Open Source Culture so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ansible101</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/ansible101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 19:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/ansible101/</guid>
      <description>In the realm of Devops, where there is always fight to provide the better and efficient ways of production in an enterprise, Ansible is one of the solution to help enterprise achieve that. This blog post will brief you about what ansible is and how learning ansible can save hours of debugging and setting up the same configurations again and again. Later this post will brief the &amp;ldquo;Ansible 101&amp;rdquo; session taken by @trishna_g at #dgplug on freenode server, IRC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog announcement</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/blog-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 14:33:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/blog-announcement/</guid>
      <description>My voice! We all have something to say and share our views with others, right? We all want to speak our opinions without any hesitation, and share our point of view, don&amp;rsquo;t we? And still, at times we don&amp;rsquo;t share everything we want to. We all have something to say, don&amp;rsquo;t we? And we all speak our feelings, our emotions whenever we want to share something with someone, right?
But at times, based on the situation, either we don&amp;rsquo;t put forward our feelings, our views and stays silent, which is by the way, not good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old is Gold!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/older-posts.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 13:07:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/older-posts.md/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for posts older than the ones present here? You can find them at https://phi2infinity.blogspot.in. All the older posts will be updated there only. I may or may not migrate the posts back to this website. Meanwhile all my writings are compiled at one place on github.
To know more, read the moving announcement here.
I am listing down all the posts available there with their title and the hyperlink to the original blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:43:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/projects/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t have much to showcase other than my blog over here. If you like, check out my profile on twitter and github to find out more about me and my projects.
Projects I am working on or I am part of:
 Dhwani (WIP) Decompiled Podcast  Communities I represent and the ones that helped me grow:
 DGPLUG India Linux User Group Delhi Pydelhi #LearnandTeach channel on freenode IRC</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about me!</title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 23:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! I am Mohit Bansal, a Computer Science Engineer based of New Delhi, India, and I am a philomath. I like advocating for Open Source Technologies, concerns for Data privacy and loves to learn. I love to learn everything and Everyone is a teacher or source of knowledge for me. But to be specific, I love simplicity in complexity and Physics, mathematics and Computers fascinates me the most. I am a Learner in general and my daily jobs includes, reading, writing and learning through, books, videos, blog and Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/at-a-glace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/at-a-glace/</guid>
      <description>To create a resume, at a glance to cover up all the gaps in the resume for the specific job</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/gallery/</guid>
      <description>May be point to flickr or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/others/meetups/scotlug-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theknowledgeseeker.in/posts/others/meetups/scotlug-meetup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>